So far, we've been stimulating event outcomes by generating
我们用 NumPy 的 random.randint 和 random.choice 生成随机数
random numbers with NumPy's random.randint and random.choice.
模拟了事件结果
However, there is a better function for
但是 模拟大型二项实验 例如掷硬币
simulating large binomial experiments like coin flips.
有一个更好的函数
Here, you see NumPy's random.binomial function,
这里可以看到 NumPy 的 random.binomial (随机二项) 函数
which simulates a number of events n,
模拟事件数量 n
which each have probability of success p.
每个事件的成功概率是 p
Success just represents one of the two outcomes of the event.
成功是事件两个结果的其中之一
Really, either outcome could be the success.
两个结果中的一个就是成功
For example, if our event is flipping a fair coin 10 times,
例如 如果我们的事件是把一枚公平硬币掷 10 次
we could define success as the number of heads.
我们可以把成功定义为正面朝上的次数
n would be the number of flips.
n 是掷硬币的次数
In this case, 10,
现在这种情况下是 10
and p would be the probability of heads for each flip which is 0.5.
p 是每次抛掷时正面朝上的概率 即 0.5
To try this out,
我们试验一下
let's set n equal to 10 and p equal to 0.5.
设 n 等于 10 p 等于 0.5
Notice, this returns 1 integer instead of an array of 10 outcomes.
注意 返回的是 1 个整数 而不是 10 个结果的数组
Since this function is only for binomial outcomes,
由于这个函数仅适用于二项结果
it can simplify the output by just returning the number of successes.
可以通过返回成功次数简化输出
In this case, 4.
现在这种情况下是 4
This is the number of heads.
这是正面朝上的次数
Again, we can run the simulation many times.
我们可以进行多次模拟
Let's run this 20 times.
我们进行 20 次
Each number in this array represents the number of
这个数组中的每个数字代表每次实验中
heads that resulted from each test of 10 coin flips.
正面朝上的次数 每次实验掷 10 次硬币
This is the number of heads on the first 10 coin flips,
这是第一次实验中掷10 次硬币正面朝上的次数
while this one is the number on the second 10 coin flips and so on,
这个是第二次实验中掷 10 次硬币正面朝上的次数 等等
for 20 different flippings of the coin.
总共 20 次实验
Let's find the mean number of heads for these tests.
我们算一下这些实验中正面朝上的平均次数
Since this is a fair coin,
由于这是一枚公平硬币
we would expect this mean to be close to 5.
我们预计这个均值接近 5
You can see that this is a little bit of a ways away,
可以看出 这个结果稍微有些偏差
probably because we only ran 20 tests.
可能是因为我们只进行了 20 次实验
Let's see what happens if we increase the number of tests.
我们看一下 如果增加实验次数 会发生什么
Since these events are random,
由于这些事件是随机的
it's not guaranteed that each simulation will perfectly average five heads.
无法保证每次模拟都能完全平均地获得五次正面
However, as this number of tests increase,
但是 随着实验次数的增加
the simulation more closely reflects the fairness of the coin.
模拟结果能更好地反映硬币的公平性
With 10,000 tests, the mean is much closer to five heads.
在进行 1 万次实验的情况下 均值更接近五次正面
Let's use matplotlib to plot a histogram of the outcomes in this simulation.
我们用 matplotlib 绘制这次模拟结果的直方图
As expected, the distribution is centered around five heads.
和预期一样 分布情况是集中在五次正面周围